[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which small software is actually a software giant from Redmond?", "correct_answer": "Microsoft", "incorrect_answers": ["Milisoft", "Nanosoft", "Minisoft"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is a ground-breaking law of linguistics first formulated in 1822. It highlights in a most intriguing way how European languages may have evolved since ancient times.", "correct_answer": "Grimms Law", "incorrect_answers": ["Kissingers  Law", "Einsteins  Law", "Schwarzeneggers  Law"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is not used by Sam and the Frog Brothers to kill vampires in the film The Lost Boys?", "correct_answer": "water balloons filled with holy water", "incorrect_answers": ["bows and arrows", "a bathtub of garlic", "wooden stakes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How old was Top Dollar from the movie The Crow, when his father told him that childhoods over the moment you know youre gonna die?", "correct_answer": "Five", "incorrect_answers": ["Nine", "Four", "Six"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress portrayed Leeloo in the 1997 science fiction movie The Fifth Element?", "correct_answer": "Milla Jovovich", "incorrect_answers": ["Angelina Jolie", "Christina Ricci", "Sigourney Weaver"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Russian city, founded by Grand Duke George II of Russia in 1221, was called Gorky from 1932 to 1990.", "correct_answer": "Nizhny Novgorod", "incorrect_answers": ["Okastock", "Vladivostock", "St. Okasburgh"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1980 movie Motel Hell there is a sign that reads It takes all kinds of critters to make Farmer Vincents fritters.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "\u201cWattle and daub is a method of construction.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which character from the 1988 movie Beetlejuice said, Live people ignore the strange and unusual. I myself am strange and unusual?", "correct_answer": "Lydia", "incorrect_answers": ["Beetlejuice", "Charles", "Barbara"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Human skin has the unique ability to acquire a darker shade when exposed to UV-rays. What animals share this ability with us?", "correct_answer": "Pigs and hammerhead sharks", "incorrect_answers": ["Dolphins and seals", "Chimpanzees and gorillas", "All reptiles and anthropoid apes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the last words that John Dillinger says in the Public Enemies 2009 movie?", "correct_answer": "Tell Billie for me Bye bye Blackbird.", "incorrect_answers": ["Man should never forget where he comes from, and where hes going.", "All is far behind me. I am ready.", "Crime does not pay, Anna."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which ancient language is often referred to as the the mother of all languages?", "correct_answer": "Sanskrit", "incorrect_answers": ["Tamil", "Latin", "Hebrew"]}]